gitex.com 2014-03-16

# GITEX TECHNOLOGY WEEK 12-16 Oct 2014 - Privacy Policy

Dubai World Trade Centre L.L.C. respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it. We provide this Privacy Statement to inform you of our Privacy Policy and practices, and of the choices you can make about what information is collected, the manner in which that information is collected and how that information is used.

The gitex.com website and its sub-domains are owned by Dubai World Trade Centre L.L.C., trading as Dubai World Trade Centre, a limited liability company incorporated in Dubai, United Arab Emirates, and having its principal office at Dubai International Convention and Exhibition Centre, Sheik Zayed Road, Convention Gate, P.O. Box 9292, Dubai, UAE. Telephone: +971-4-3321000, Fax: +971-4-3312173.

For the purposes of this Privacy Statement "we", "our" and "us" refer to Dubai World Trade Centre L.L.C., "this website" collectively refers to the dwtc.com website and its sub-domains, and "you" and "your" refer to a specific individual or program accessing this website.

**Governance**  
This website is governed in accordance with the laws of the Emirate of Dubai and the applicable federal laws of the United Arab Emirates. The courts of the Emirate of Dubai in the United Arab Emirates shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any dispute arising out of your use of this website.

**Data automatically collected**  
We collect the domain name and Internet Protocol address (IP address) of the computer from which or the first identifiable computer through which you access this website automatically. This information does not identify you as an individual, but only the computer from which or the first identifiable computer through which you access this website.

This information is used to help us better understand this website's usage, so that we can improve our service to you and may also be used to provide content on this website relevant to your geographic region, including, but not limited to advertisements and promotions. We do not link information automatically collected by such means with personal information about you.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer when requested by a website. They do not compromise your privacy or security, as each cookie can only be read by the same website that requested your browser to store the cookie.

We request your browser to store a cookie when you access this website and may request your browser to store one or more cookies when you make purchases, request or personalise information, or register yourself for certain services. Unless you explicitly opt to store additional information, our cookies only contain one or more sequential computer-generated identifiers. The cookies this website requests your browser to store are suffixed with "dwtc.com" and expire at the very latest after 365 days from the date on which they were last updated. This information is used to help us better understand this website's usage, so that we can improve our service to you and may also be used to provide content on this website based on your previous visits, including, but not limited to advertisements and promotions. Unless you explicitly opt to store additional information, we do not link information automatically collected by such means with personal information about you. Accepting to store the cookies requested by this website does not give us access to your personal information, but we may use the cookies to identify your computer. Most browsers automatically store cookies by default, but you can choose to refuse or selectively accept to store certain cookies by adjusting the preferences in your browser. However, if your browser refuses to store cookies, some features of this website may not be available to you and some pages on this website may not display properly. You can find information on popular browsers and how to adjust your cookie preferences at the following websites:

  * Microsoft Internet Explorer: <http://www.microsoft.com/>
  * Netscape Navigator: <http://www.netscape.com/>
  * Mozilla Firefox: <http://www.mozilla.org/>
  * Opera: [http://www.opera.com](http://www.opera.com/)/

Additionally, browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer 6 and Netscape 7.0 feature The Platform for Privacy Preferences (P3P) technology, which gives you the ability to make informed choices about the use of your personal information online. P3P-enabled browsers can be configured to automatically accept or refuse to store cookies, based on whether a website's P3P compact policy file meets your privacy preferences. We will make every effort to provide a P3P compact policy file for each cookie that this website requests your browser to store.

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).  Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage.  Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.  You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.  By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

**Data collection and use**  
When you request information through this website, we may need to know some personal information about you. When emailing us, or subscribing for information we will need your e-mail address, name and other limited personal identifiers. If you choose to purchase information, goods, products or services, we will usually require some additional limited financial details. Where you request employment related services or products we will usually need limited data about personal identifiers, education, employment, family and financial details. Your personal data will be processed to provide information, goods, products and services you request in the form that you require.

Most of this information may be used by us to enable us to review, develop and improve the services which we offer and provide you with information we think you will find valuable. Sensitive information such as your credit card details will only be used for the purpose of processing payment and will not be used for any other purposes. We will not share your details with any third party without your explicit permission, unless required by law enforcement action, or local law. The information you submit may be transferred outside of the country from which you may be accessing this website, and may be transferred to countries which do not have data protection laws or to countries where your privacy and other fundamental rights will not be protected as extensively. These and all other transmissions will remain secure and under our sole control.

If we look to use your personal data for a new purpose, beyond what it was originally provided for, we will ask for your explicit consent.

**Data retention**  
Your data may be held for up to 2 years after the termination of your relationship with us for the purposes of improving our services offered, after which time it is depersonalised and non-identifiable. We do not collect any additional information about you other than that outlined above.

**Access to your personal data**  
You have the right to see personal information we keep about you upon payment of a fee. To enquire about accessing your personal information please send an email to [data@dwtc.com](mailto:data@dwtc.com?subject=Privacy%20Pledge%20Enquiry), or send postal mail to the following address:

Dubai World Trade Centre L.L.C.  
P.O. Box 9292, Dubai, UAE

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data that we keep about you, within 40 days; subject to the provision of proof of your identity.

**Disclosure and Visitor choice**  
You may unsubscribe or opt-out of our services at any time. Where we disclose your personal data for those purposes stated, we provide you with the means to opt-out of disclosure by either indicating in a box at the point of the website where personal data is collected, by sending an email to [data@dwtc.com](mailto:data@dwtc.com) or by sending postal mail to the following address:

Dubai World Trade Centre L.L.C.  
P.O. Box 9292, Dubai, UAE

Where we disclose your personal data for purposes, which are different to those, stated we offer you the opportunity to consent prior to disclosure.

**Children**  
We are committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and we do not target our websites to children under 13.

**Security**  
We are committed to protecting the information you provide us. We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control, in accordance with the laws of the Emirate of Dubai in the United Arab Emirates and the applicable federal laws of the United Arab Emirates. The security measures are designed to prevent unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification and unlawful destruction or accidental loss.

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. SSL encryption is designed to make the information unreadable by anyone but us. This security measure is working when you see either the symbol of an unbroken key or closed lock (depending on your browser) on the bottom of your browser window. You should be aware that no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as totally secure. Although we strive to protect such information, we do not guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us over the Internet and you do so at your own risk. If you do not feel it is appropriate to send information electronically, please contact +971 (4) 3312000 for an alternative way of conducting business.

**Privacy compliance**  
We are voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure. Data privacy legislation is subject to revision and we suggest that you regularly check our Privacy Policy.

**Hyperlinks**  
Our websites may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience. If you access those links, you will leave our website. We do not control those websites or their privacy practices, which may differ from ours. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. This Privacy Policy does not cover the personal data you choose to give to unrelated third parties. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy of any company before submitting your personal information. Some third-party companies may choose to share their personal data with us; that sharing is governed by that third-party company's privacy policy.

**Notification of changes**  
We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Your continued access or use of this website after such changes indicates your acceptance of the Privacy Policy as modified. It is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy regularly. This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 6th 2009. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by way of an email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**Contacting us**  
This privacy policy sets out in broad terms how we handle your personal information and safeguard our privacy. If you have any questions relating to our Privacy Policy send postal mail to the following address:

The Data Officer  
Dubai World Trade Centre L.L.C.  
P.O. Box 9292, Dubai, UAE

**Website**  
[ASP](http://www.aspevents.net/privacy) provide and host this website for DWTC. [ASP](http://www.aspevents.net/privacy) is registered with the UK Data Commissioner as Data Controllers and hold all the data within the UK.

**Copyright**  
Copyright © DWTC 2014. All rights reserved. The users of this website may reproduce materials available in the website for authorised users and potential users of GITEX 2013. DWTC requires that the following statement be included in all reproductions of this material:

Copyright © DWTC 2014. All rights reserved. Reprinted with the permission of DWTC. Except for these specified uses, no part of the materials available in any the DWTC website may be copied, photocopied, reproduced, translated or reduced to any electronic medium or machine-readable form, in whole or in part, without prior written consent of DWTC. Any other reproduction in any form without the permission of DWTC is prohibited. Distribution for commercial purposes is prohibited.

**Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitation of Liability**  
DWTC uses reasonable care in publishing materials available in DWTC websites. However, DWTC does not guarantee their accuracy or completeness. Materials available in DWTC websites are provided “as is” with no warranty, express or implied, and all such warranties hereby disclaimed.

DWTC assumes no liability for any loss, damage or expense from errors or omissions in the materials available in DWTC  
websites, whether arising in contract or otherwise.
